Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1944-2003 (bulk 1959-1994) MS 3009-RG 6
New-York Historical Society
- Series I.B. Editor-in-Chief Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, 1944-1998 (bulk 1968-1987); 75 Linear feet in 75 record cartons
  - Subseries I.B.6. Speeches, 1970-1986; 6 Linear feet in 6 record cartons
    - 1981: March: Denver Speech Materials (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 14)
    - 1981: March 18: Denver, CO: Time Inc. Dinner (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 14-15)
    - 1981: April 14: Montreal: Speech to Canada's Business Council on National Interests (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 16)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side B label: "Montreal Speech Do not erase."
    - 1981: June 7: Iona College Commencement Address (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 17)
    - 1981: September 30-October 4: Western American Association of Advertising Agencies, Inc. Convention and Speech (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 18)
    - 1981: December 15: Birmingham, AL: Talk to Goodrich's Club (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 19)
      1 audiocassette: analog; 1 15/16 x 1 5/16 in., 1/8 in. tape. On side A label: "BERM."
    - 1982: March 22: Captiva Island, FL: Public Affairs Conference: "How the Press Is Seen Today" (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 20)
    - 1982: June 7: Yale University: Volunteer Speech (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 21)
    - 1982: August 1: Santa Fe, NM: St. Johns College: "The Press: Hero or Villain?" (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 22)
    - 1982: October 13: Foreign Policy Association Talk (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 23)
    - 1982: November 15: Silurians (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 24)
    - 1983: February 7: Talk at Newsweek's 50th Anniversary (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 25)
    - 1983: March 20: Cancun: Life Sales Meeting (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 26)
    - 1983: May 8: Bennett College Commencement (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 27)
    - 1983: May 26: Foreign Policy Association: George Shultz Introduction (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 28)
    - 1983: December 9: ASME [American Society of Magazine Editors] Speech: "The Art of Editing" (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 29)
    - 1984: June 27: Lincoln Center: Remarks at People's Tenth Anniversary Party (Offsite-box 1048, Folder 30)
    - 1984: July 28: Martha's Vineyard: Politics and Power Seminar (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 1)
    - 1984: September 18: Talk to Advertising Women of New York (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 2)
    - 1984: November 15: New York University: Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 3)
    - 1984: December 8: 20th Century Fund Dinner (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 4)
    - 1985: February 4: Talk to Time-Life Alumni Association (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 5)
    - 1985: February 24: Washington, D.C.: Remarks at Update American for Canadian Visitors (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 6)
    - 1985: March 4: Ponte Vedra, FL: Corporate Public Affairs Conference (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 7)
    - 1985: March 20: Columbia University: In Praise of Magazines Delacorte Lecture (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 8)
    - 1985: April 2: Carefree, AZ: Time Sales Meeting (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 9)
    - 1985: May 15-18: The Greenbrier: Talk at American Association of Advertising Agencies, Inc. Annual Meeting (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 10)
    - 1985: May 22: Case Western University: Commencement Address: "The Press: Why You Can't Love It or Leave It" (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 11)
    - 1985: September 3: CM&D [Corporate Manufacturing & Distribution] Conference (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 12)
    - 1985: October 3: The Greenbrier: Talk to the Sports Illustrated Staff (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 13)
    - 1985: October 11: Foreign Policy Association Talk on Gorbachev Interviews (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 14)
    - 1986: February 6: Arthur Burns Introduction (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 15)
    - 1986: April 15: Center for Communication Talk Honoring Punch Sulzberger (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 16)
    - 1986: June 23: Time-Life Books 25th Anniversary (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 17)
    - 1987?: Grunwald Retirement (Offsite-box 1053, Folder 1-2)
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Orig." On container label: "Original Master. Henry A. Grunwald Retirement Show. Audio-1-3. Cues 2. Clock 4."
      1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in., 1/4 in. tape. On label: "Backup." On container label: "Dupe. Henry A. Grunwald Retirement Show. Audio-1-3. Cues 2. Clock 4."
    - Undated: HAG 4 (Offsite-box 1053, Folder 3)
      1 computer disc (floppy disk): 5 1/2 in. On label: "HAG 4." On containing envelope: "To Slide Transfer Service. This is the floppy disk if you want to run it off computer."
    - Undated: Slide Carousels (Offsite-box 1053-1055)
      Eleven slide carousel boxes. The slides, carousels, and boxes do not indicate titles or dates of the presentations.
  - Subseries I.B.7. Trips, 1951-1987; 4 Linear feet in 4 record cartons
    Trips taken by Grunwald are a mix of professional and personal although the professional aspect is meetings and conferences along with general fact-finding about the area. The trips seem to be separate from the Newstours. Grunwald writes notes about his impressions on his trips specifically for Africa (1966), Portugal (1975), Cuba (1979), and China (1980). Cuba also includes a transcript of Grunwald's and Richard Duncan's interview with Fidel Castro. Other items of interest include personal family correspondence in Paris and Italy (1965), and a signed photo of Julius Nyerere in Africa (1966). Other records include Time Editorial query sheets, travel itineraries, meeting agenda, event ephemera, correspondence arranging travel logistics, non-trip related work correspondence, and receipts.
    Organized chronologically by date of trip.
    - 1951-1952: Europe (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 18-19)
    - 1958: Switzerland, Italy and Austria (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 20-23)
    - 1962: Europe (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 24-25)
    - 1964: Southeast Asia (Offsite-box 1049, Folder 26-27)
    - 1965: Paris and Italy (Offsite-box 1049-1050)
    - 1966: Africa (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 2-7)
    - 1967: London (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 8)
    - 1968: Morocco (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 9)
    - 1968: London and Paris (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 10)
    - 1968: Portugal (Vacation) (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 11-12)
    - 1970: Western and Southern United States (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 13)
    - 1970: Western Europe, Greece, and Lebanon (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 14)
    - 1970: Western Europe (France, Germany, The Netherlands, Austria, United Kingdom) and Cannes Conference (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 15)
    - 1971: Latin America (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 16-17)
    - 1971: Washington, D.C. (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 18)
    - 1972: St. Maarten (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 19)
    - 1972: Europe, Japan, Hong Kong (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 20)
    - 1973: Schedules (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 21)
    - 1974: California (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 22)
    - 1974: Southern United States (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 23)
    - 1975: Portugal (Offsite-box 1050, Folder 24)
    - 1975: May [London, Russia, Poland, Turkey, Iran, Rome] (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 1)
    - 1976: Europe (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 2-4)
    - 1976: Midwest United States (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 5)
    - 1976: Houston (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 6)
    - 1977: Europe and Africa (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 7-8)
    - 1979: Moscow (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 9)
    - 1979: France (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 10)
    - 1979: European Communities (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 11)
    - 1979: Cuba and Dominican Republic (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 12-15)
    - 1980: China (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 16-17)
    - 1981: Eleuthera (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 18)
    - 1981: Eastern Europe (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 19-20)
    - 1981: Japan, Korea, and Philippines (Offsite-box 1051, Folder 21-24)
    - 1981: International Press Institute Conference in Madrid and Paris Visit (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 1)
    - 1982: England and Germany (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 2)
    - 1983: London and Paris (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 3)
    - 1983: Hamburg (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 4-5)
    - 1983: Forbes Baloon Meeting, Bayeux, Vienna, Salzburg (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 6)
    - 1983: Time London Cover Show and Talloires Voices of Freedom Conference (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 7)
    - 1983-1984: Paris and Holland (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 8)
    - 1984: Middle East (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 9)
    - 1984: Vienna, Prague, Budapest, and Paris (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 10-11)
    - 1985: London (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 12-13)
    - 1986: London and Syria: President Assad Interview (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 14)
    - 1987: Korea (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 15)
    - 1987: Moscow (Offsite-box 1052, Folder 16)
  - Subseries I.B.8. Archives Transfer Forms, 1984-1987, 1998; 0.3 Linear feet in 3 folders
    The archives transfer forms transferred groups of records from Grunwald's office to the Time Inc. Archives and originally were filed at the front of each section of transfers. The form indicates the office of origination, staff member of origination, the person transferring the records, the series, and the date ranges of the records. During processing of the Henry Anatole Grunwald Files, the archives transfer forms were removed and retained as administrative records.
    Organized to reflect the order of the subseries.
    - Archives Transfer Forms, 1984-1987, 1998 (Offsite-box 1056, Folder 5-7)
- Series I.C. Editor-in-Chief Jason McManus Files, 1951-1994 (bulk 1987-1994); 13 Linear feet in 13 record cartons
  Jason McManus started at Time Inc. in 1957 as a Sports Illustrated summer trainee. The next year, he was a Time-Life News Service trainee. Time Inc. hired him in 1959, and he held various writing and editor positions with Time through 1974, including launching the European edition. In 1976, he was promoted to Time Assistant Managing Editor then Time Executive Editor in 1978. From 1982 to 1983, the corporate editorial department selected him to serve a temporary assignment as Assistant Corporate Editor while continuing to hold his permanent position. After this temporary position, he served one year as Corporate Editor then two years as Time Managing Editor before his appointment as Editor-in-Chief in 1987. During his tenure, Time Inc. executed the major merger that produced Time Warner. McManus retired in 1994.
  The Jason McManus Files primarily are during his tenure as Editor-in-Chief with some records from earlier in his career. Records include his day-to-day file, correspondence, departmental files, and travel records.
  Organized into four subseries:
  Subseries I.C.1. Chron File
  Subseries I.C.2. Memoranda and Correspondence
  Subseries I.C.3. Departmental Files
  Subseries I.C.4. Trips
  - Subseries I.C.1. Chron File, 1992-1993; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Chron File is McManus's record of day-to-day memoranda and other correspondence sent out from his office. The contents of the folders are arranged in reverse chronological order. Frequent addressees include All Staff, Reginald Brack (President, CEO, and Chairman), Don Logan (President and CEO), and heads of various departments.
    - 1992: Memos (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 9-12)
    - 1992: Letters (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 13-16)
    - 1992: Memos to Managing Editors (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 17)
    - 1993: Memos (Offsite-box 1200-1201)
    - 1993: Letters (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 5-8)
  - Subseries I.C.2. Memoranda and Correspondence, 1976-1991; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Correspondence contains McManus's incoming and outgoing correspondence. Topics include staff changes, responses to invitations, complaints and responses regarding articles, and general exchanges with other companies and organizations. No folder for 1983 found.
    Organized into Memoranda, arranged alphabetically with General at the front, and Correspondence, arranged chronologically.
    - Memos: General Outgoing, 1969-1991 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 9-13)
    - Memoranda: To Ray Cave, 1986 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 14)
    - Memoranda: To Henry Grunwald, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 15-16)
    - Memos: To Managing Editors, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 1-3)
    - Memos: To Staff, 1981-1994 (Offsite-box 1201, Folder 17-20)
    - Correspondence: 1981 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: 1982 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: 1984 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: 1985 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: 1986 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 8-9)
    - Correspondence: Time Managing Editor Congratulations, 1986 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: 1987 (Offsite-box 1202, Folder 11-14)
    - Correspondence: Editor-in-Chief Notes of Congratulations, 1987 (Offsite-box 1202-1203)
    - Correspondence: 1988 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 2-6)
    - Correspondence: 1988 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Correspondence: 1989 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 7-11)
    - Correspondence: 1989 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Correspondence: 1990 (Offsite-box 1203, Folder 12-16)
    - Correspondence: 1991 (Offsite-box 1203-1204)
  - Subseries I.C.3. Departmental Files, 1951-1994; 9 Linear feet in 9 record cartons
    The Departmental Files are McManus's office files on various projects and subjects. This is also where McManus collected correspondence sent out by prior editors-in-chief Hedley Donovan and Henry Grunwald. Records include invitations to serve on boards (Boy Scouts); articles on the Time Warner merger; protest letters on advertisements published in Time Inc.'s magazines (Condom Ads and Feminist Complaints); memoranda about the information reference services provided by Edit Services; memoranda and reports reviewing problems or required retooling of the magazines (Fortune: Bias and Time: Task Force); the complaint letter from the staff organization Lesbians and Gay Men at Time Warner with annotations by McManus (Gay Complaints); proposals for collaboration with television networks regarding News on Demand; correspondence about possible book publication (Schwarzkopf); registration materials for the staff softball team; and memoranda discussing the first issue of Martha Stewart Living. The term "memorabilia" in titles refers to papers, not objects. Two archives transfer forms found stapled to the front of files are at the end.
    - Archives/Elaine Felsher, 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 4)
    - Asian American Journalists Association, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 5)
    - Asiaweek: General, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 6-8)
    - Asiaweek: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Asiaweek: Michael O'Neill, 1989-1994 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 9-11)
    - Asiaweek: Michael O'Neill [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Asiaweek: Yazhou Zhoukan, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 12)
    - Boston/Mystery Guest Lunch, 1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 13)
    - Boy Scouts, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 14)
    - CNN (Turner), 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 15)
    - CNN (Turner) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Connie Bruck: New Yorker Piece, 1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 16)
    - Bryson, John, 1988 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 17)
    - Cave, Ray: Memoranda, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 18-19)
    - Clurman, Richard: Time Book, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 20)
    - Compensation, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 21)
    - Condom Ads, 1989 (Offsite-box 1204, Folder 22)
    - Corporate Policy Committee Meetings, 1993 (Offsite-box 1204-1205)
    - Custom Publishing, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 2)
    - Donovan, Hedley: General, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 3)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Memoranda, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 4)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Staff Memoranda, 1967-1978 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 5)
    - Donovan, Hedley: Speeches, 1970-1976 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 6)
    - Edit Management Meeting, 1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 7)
    - Edit Services, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 8)
    - Entertainment Weekly, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 9-10)
    - Family Wealth, 1988 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 11-12)
    - Feminist Complaints, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 13)
    - First Amendment, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 14)
    - First Amendment [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Fortune: General, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 15-16)
    - Fortune: Bias, 1990 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 17)
    - Fortune: International, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 18)
    - Fortune Espana, 1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 19)
    - Fortune France: General, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 20)
    - Fortune France: Board Meetings, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1205, Folder 21-22)
    - Fortune Italia, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 1)
    - Gay Complaints, 1987-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 2)
    - Globe Review, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 3)
    - Goodman, Mark [RESTRICTED UNTIL 2029], 1994 (Offsite-box R19)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Memoranda, 1951-1978 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 4-8)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Retirement, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 9)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Retirement [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Grunwald, Henry: Speeches, 1968-1987 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 10-11)
    - Guild, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 12)
    - Gulf War Coverage, 1991 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 13)
    - Halasz, Piri, 1987 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 14)
    - HBO, 1989 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 15)
    - In Style, 1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 16)
    - Interns, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 17)
    - International Press Institute, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 18)
    - Kamsky, Ginny: China Project, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 19)
    - Kamsky, Ginny: China Project [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R19)
    - Legal Department [RESTRICTED], 1987-1993 (Offsite-box R19, R23)
    - Library, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 20)
    - Life, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 21-22)
    - Life Weekly, 1991 (Offsite-box 1206, Folder 23-24)
    - Limbo, Inday [RESTRICTED], 1994 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Little, Brown, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 1)
    - Little, Brown [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Luce, Henry, III, 1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 2)
    - Luce, Henry: Biographer, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 3)
    - Luce, Henry: Biographer [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - March of Time: Musical Adaptation Outline, 1978 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Group Strategy, 1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 5)
    - Maidstone Management Meeting, 1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 6-7)
    - Man of the Year Booklet by National Portrait Gallery, 1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 8)
    - McManus in Paris for Time Europe Launch, 1973 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 9)
    - McManus/Norman Pearlstine Dinner, 1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 10)
      Pearlstine succeeded McManus as Editor-in-Chief.
    - Memorabilia, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 11-12)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 13)
    - Memoranda: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Mentoring, 1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 14)
    - Miller, Bob, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 15)
    - Money, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 16-17)
    - Morrison Special Projects, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 18)
    - Muller, Henry, 1992 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 19)
    - New Magazines/Joint Ventures, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 20-21)
    - News on Demand, 1993 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 22-23)
    - News on Demand [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - 1968 Project, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 24)
    - 1980 Committee, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 1207, Folder 25)
      Includes Edit Task Force material.
    - Pan Am 103 Story in Time, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 1)
    - Patricia Ryan Salute from Ann Fadiman, 1987 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 2)
    - Papandreou, Andreas, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 3)
    - Papandreou, Andreas [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - People, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 4-5)
    - President's Advisory Panel on International Edicational Exchange, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 6)
    - Roger Rosenblatt/Steve Ross Letters, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 7)
    - Ross, Steve, 1989-1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 8)
    - Russian Meeting (Publishing Committee USSR), 1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 9)
    - Saar, John [RESTRICTED], 1992 (Offsite-box R23)
    - Salzburg Seminar, 1992 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 10)
    - Schiavone Construction Company, 1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 11)
    - Schiavone Construction Company [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Schwarzkopf, H. Norman, 1991 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 12)
    - Softball, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 13)
    - South Africa, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 14)
    - Sports Illustrated: General, 1987-1994 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 15-16)
    - Sports Illustrated: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Sports Illustrated: Swim Suit Issue, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 17)
    - Sports Illustrated for Kids, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 18)
    - Stewart, Martha, 1990 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 19)
    - Takeover Suggestions from Staff, 1989 (Offsite-box 1208, Folder 20)
    - Thank You Notes and Complaints, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 21)
    - Time: General, 1986-1994 (Offsite-box 1208-1209)
    - Time: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R23)
    - Time: Articles On, 1969-1972 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 2)
    - Time: Lloyd Cutler on Kramer Piece, 1994 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 3)
    - Time: Polish in SS, 1994 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 4)
    - Time: Task Force, 1991 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 5-7)
    - Time Australia, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 8-9)
    - Time Canada, 1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 10)
    - Time Nihonban, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 11)
    - Time Inc.: Articles on Time Inc. Strike, 1976 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 12)
    - Time Inc.: Speeches, 1970-1988 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 13)
    - Time Warner: Board Meeting: Lyford Cay, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 14-15)
    - Time Warner: Books About, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 16)
    - Time Warner: Merger: In-House Stories, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 17)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Outside Stories, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 18)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Bernstein New York Times Article, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 19)
    - Time Warner: Merger: Brucker New Yorker Article, 1989 (Offsite-box 1209, Folder 20)
    - Together Dummy, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 1)
    - TV Cable Week: Postmortem, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 2)
    - TV Cable Week: Task Force, 1983 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 3)
    - United Way, 1993 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 4)
    - Video Weekly, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 5-6)
    - Wall Street Journal Article on CEO Pay Survey/Graf Crystal, 1991 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 7)
    - Wall Street Journal on Time, 1993 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 8)
    - Watergate Memorabilia, 1974 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 9)
    - Who (People Australia), 1993-1994 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 10)
    - Woman Dummy, 1977 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 11)
    - Archives Transfer Forms, 1994 (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 23)
  - Subseries I.C.4. Trips, 1986-1992; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    Trips contains business travel files and include correspondence, itineraries, background information on people and places, travel notes from McManus and others, and copies of travel documents.
    - 1986 May: France, Germany, Moscow (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 12)
    - 1986 November: Far East (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 13)
    - 1987-1988: China, Hong Kong, Japan (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 14)
    - 1988 February: London and Milan with Reginald Brack (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 15)
    - 1988 November: Paris and Milan (Fortune France and Fortune Italia) (Offsite-box 1210, Folder 16)